# Jon Dyson

Full Stack Developer

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Self motivated and adaptive full stack developer, with several years of experience in small team project oriented environments. Previously founded a technology driven startup, which included direct development work as well as the management of contracted development. Possesses a strong background in financial risk assessment and financial feasibility studies

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Lotus Import Group** – Founder (Full Stack Dev), 2014 – 16

Created a portfolio of ecommerce websites focused on the manufacture, importation, and direct sales of a variety of consumer goods.

# **US Army** - Civil Affairs Operator, 2008 - 16

Civil Affairs Operators deploy in small teams and function autonomously to develop and implement small to large scale cultural and economic projects and programs. Planning often begins and ends with a detailed financial feasibility study.

# International Financial Group - Underwriting, 2011-14

Responsible for providing both a business risk, financial risk assessment of commercial general liability in the high risk excess and surplus lines market. Policy risk exposure ranged from 2M to 10M aggregate.

### **EDUCATION**

# **RefactorU**, CO— Full Stack Immersion Course, 2016

Graduated from the RefactorU immersion learning program focused on MEAN stack development.

# **UConn**, CT— Bachelor's Degree (BGS), 2010

Graduated with a concentration in Sociology and a minor in economics from The University of Connecticut.

# Special Operations Center of Excellence, NC - CivilAffairs Operator, 2008

Graduated from the US Army's Special Warfare Center & School in the top 5% of the class (Commandant's List)







#### JonDyson.com

hello@jondyson.com linkedin.com/in/jon-dyson github.com/DysonJ 860.309.5343

#### **SKILLS**

Technical

Javascript

**Angular** 

Node.js

Express.js

MongoDB

Git

**jQuery** 

CSS

Materialize

Bootstrap

Stylus

mySQL

msAccess

HTML

ColdFusion

Professional Development

Toastmasters: 1 Year



## **AWARDS**

### **Army Commendation Medal**

Awarded for rapid assimilation and cultural understanding in an austere environment.

Commandant's List

Graduated from the Army's Special Warfare Center in the top 5% of the class.



refactor

#### CLEARANCE

DoD Security Clearance:







